my name is Eli I love comic books I'm a
classic geek I cannot find any woman
that's interested in the things I'm
interested in it reminds me of somebody
that I knew in high school he was a
little bit big so they called him big so
to compensate for all that he got a
bunch of Senseless tattoos and piercings
I beat the out of that kid every
day for 4 years let's go meet today's
lucky loser I'm big J oakerson and I'm a
comedian in my ACT I do a lot of crowd
work within that crowd work I've become
known for hooking up couples so I decide
to see if I could take my matchmaking
skills Pro and become a champion to
Underdogs
everywhere here you are J if I cannot
find you a girl who is into sci-fi and
Comics I'm going to take my Amazing
Spider-Man number one out of his
polyurethane rapper no way enough said
don't do it let's get out of here make
it Happ awesome if Jay really has a
first edition Spider-Man that's
ridiculous f adorable meet your
date for the day kitty oh hi hi I got to
say I'm pretty proud of myself I don't
think he was expecting a girl that
pretty and I happen to know she's loose
enough to let him put his dragon in her
dungeon get it he seems very nerdy and I
like nerdy he may be a little too nerdy
I am interested in looking forward to
getting to know her Eli you're in your
element I know you guys have some common
interests oh yeah comic books all kinds
of things nerd right awesome what's your
favorite comic book has to be Batman
hands down okay night get
it yeah it was a lob and I spiked it why
don't you describe your idea lightsaber
for kitty go ahead I'mma fly on the wall
you guys talk it out uh lightsabers I'm
a big fan of Anakin's lightsaber veins
big mushroom cap and the Asian Jedi have
really small
Sabers the process of getting your
lightsaber well if you're part of the
Jedi Order requires you to go and
construct your own lightsaber slow down
cold trickle you are you are over
nerding her right now Eli is weebing his
way right out of this the chances of him
getting laid right now one out of five
Ewoks Eli are you a big fan of tattoos
cuz I don't know if you've noticed but
she has all of them Eli any tattoos for
you at all only my birth mark it looks
like an egg frying wait what's it shaped
like an egg frying doesn't that mean
you're the chosen one I'm going to keep
talking to her and maybe I can just
convince her I could be her Superman I
do a great Chewbacca impression if
you're interest that we've got to hear
this you want to hear it going to be
good I'm excited
excited and then and then and then you
say all over my back do it again what do
you say we take this party somewhere
else sounds good yeah yeah all right
let's move on here we are at black
Square Tattoo Shop Eli this is where I'm
about to become the ultimate wingman for
you Captain's love star date 719 69 2B I
have to step my game up if I want this
Kitty to boldly go where no kitty has
gone before Eli's pants must get Eli
laid can't I brought you guys here to
this tattoo show cuz I think to make
this date really click you guys need a
teamwork activity and because public
69ing is illegal I went with the fifth
best thing you're going to design a
superhero tattoo that I am going to get
placed on my leg are you
[Music]
serious I don't this up for me and
don't draw a bunch of dicks I already
have three of those on my body not
including my own let's make a list of
some of the iconic Captain America
Batman right fat Wings serious balls
Kitty no testicles Kitty has this crazy
idea of adding testicles to the tattoo
to to testic
it's balls dude spit it out what
superhero specializes in testicles he'll
think it's funny no he won't matter of
fact let's see what Jay has to say about
it fine what's going on she wants to
brok down on your tattoo there's no
point to that well here's how I'm
feeling I love the pentagram because I'm
Jewish not a big fan of the balls but
hey how about this we can split the
difference I'll get this tattoo on my
balls I'm kidding I'm not doing that I
will get this tattoo the pentagram the
wings on my leg right now I have a
feeling these balls are going on this
tattoo either
way in the best case scenario this
tattoo is going to last way longer than
this relationship but Kitty did design
this tattoo primarily herself so maybe
there's a chance for me to move in there
either way tonight I'll be bent over a
stool it's officially the Moment of
Truth currently being marked for life
was it all worth it but here's where we
find out right now you have a decision
to make I'm holding two cards a hotel
room key where you guys will leave here
and go and do God knows what or in this
hand I have a metro pass and you go your
separate ways I'm going to count to
three and you are either going to throw
up a thumbs up or a thumbs
down one hi
two three no
testicles
fire
well me
running all right man you're all done
yes I am Kitty is a pretty cool person
but she may not be my Superwoman it
wasn't going to work really I should
have just went home with Jay uh I'm
still
here